https://cobblawfirm.com/privacy-policy/

Contact/Email
(850) 423-0035
About UsStephen G. CobbLegal ProcessFlorida Criminal Defense Legal GroupOur Office LocationsPractice AreasExpungementForgeryFraudDiscovery LawBrain ImagingMental HealthMotions To Suppress EvidenceCommunity Control ViolationsViolent CrimesTheft DefenseSex CrimesArrest PreventionDriving OffensesPlea BargainFirearms CrimesComputer CrimesResisting ArrestFelonyDUIDrug CrimesProperty CrimeMilitary ArrestsJuvenile CrimesTrespassLocationsDestinFort Walton BeachMonticelloCrestviewCounties ServedResultsVideosOur Youtube channel videosGeneral VideosTestimonialsClient TestimonialsLawyer EndorsementsNewsBlogPaymentContact Us
Call For Free Consultation(850) 423-0035Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Get Help Now
Home > Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyTerms Of UseDisclaimerNav MapBlogResourcesContact UsLawyer MarketingNav Map
225 Main Street, Suite 7-G Destin, FL 32540
850-423-0035
Prices Vary
Criminal Defense Attorney Florida
-
5 star rating - based on 5 reviews in FacebookWe serve military and civilian clients in Destin, Fort Walton Beach, Sandestin, Niceville and all of Okaloosa and Walton Counties.
Copyright © 2020, Stephen G. Cobb - Florida Criminal Defense Lawyer. All rights reserved.
